JOB OBJECTIVE Indexing/Administrative Staff.
SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS:
Experienced administrative staRAseistat, Loan Processor. Appointment Setter, in charge of miscellanerus bars & $55 Deduction of Employees and dients Phineath payments, MS Excel, &t
Office. PowerPoint, With Encoding & typing skills, Pety cach custodian. Dligent and a hard worker, muti-tasks, able to take instructions with or without supervision
EDUCATION:
Graduated, BS Commerce, Major in Computer Science, Colegio de San Agustin, Bacolod City
Graduated, High School, University of Negros OccidentalRexlee, Talisay City
PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:
Barangay Personn/staff
Barangay Zane 1, Talisay City
Barangay state and record keeper, Encode data using Excel and Word, write final minutes of the session, issuing cedula, receipts, Business Permits, barangay certifcations, indigency,
residency, and other special certifications, fling of necessary documents related to berangay, submits reports to DILG, reliever to the Secretary.
Office Secretary
Pict Travel Ticketing Office, Talisay City
Recapfonist, tinerary ticketing agent, Maintain and upkeep Inventories, Reconciled income & cash collectione, cash on hands & fquid capital.
Ceposit money in the bank in charge of bilings and uilty payments and records of building occupants and checking and maintaining functionalties of facilities and premises.
+
Encoder, Loyola Plans Inc., Bacolod City
Sheryl V. Meguizo
11 Salvador Lacson St,Gambce Subdivision, Zona 1. Talisay City
Mobil:09173108827-Email: mark.mequizo@amail.com
Management Information System Officant Administrativa StaffiLoan Processor
Mentors Philippines, Pasig City & Cebu City
Data Entry, in charge of release payroll checks, Processed of Loans, checks, accident insurance & IDs, personal passbooks of the diants, fire records of employees.
Entertained microfinance oficers & client's inquiries, reliever to accounts oficer & cashier, prepared training schedules for director & Board of Directors signatories, officiators.
Bank reconctiafon & vafdated personal savings balance of the clients, generated monthly & weakly accurate & timely reports for program, area & branch managers.
Answered calls, incoming faxes &inquiries zom cients & officers, ale and sare keep of confidential credits investigations, tens utility check, Discrepancy reports.
Projectirepection, violation report & other sensitive information, in charge of petty cash, office supplies, ensures & reports the reability of orice equipments.
Encoded dients information, maternity & death insurance daine. Petty cash custodian & deposited cash in the bank.
TraineelApprentica, Social Security System, Bacolod City
Processed employees maternity & death benefits. Reviewed applications & documents request from the 555 members.
* Aided supervisor's instructions and nits.
TRAININGS AND SEMINARS:
+
+
Freparing and Cocking Holmests NC 1 Teada
Hand Spa, Manicure and Pedicure, NC 2, Teada
Silkacreen Printing Short Course, Gander & Development Livelihood Program
FLFI Ofice, Livefhood Buiking, Pasig City
Career Workshop
Ayala Life FGU Building, Cebu City
English Speaking Program
Salinas Drive Lahug, Cebu City
Management Information System Officer & Account Officer Training
Morayla, Metro Mania
Accounts Officer & Cashier Training Workshop
F. Manala Avenue, Malinao, Pasig City
VOLUNTEER SERVICE:
Rover Scout Circle 40, Pasig City Manila, Philippines
Facilitated Rover Orientation, Vigil & Investiture Ceremony. Community Service, Team Building & Rappel Activities.
1997
1992
2001-2010
Full-Time Volunteer Non-Profit Organization, Manila, Philippines
Inifated community service. Weeky budgeting, assessed & prepared performance Reports.
REFERENCES: Submission upon requset
2013
2000
1996-1997
2022
2019
2012
2010
2010
2008
2004
2003 2004
2018-2023
1997 1969